I hear your sales are doing quite well.
Thanks to your help, they have been
rising since the Kuryu Fujiwara scandal.
Please, it's all thanks
to your skill as editor-in-chief.
Thank you for next year's
calendar deal as well.
The executives are thrilled.
I expect you'll be promoted soon.
Perhaps you'll become
the next managing director?
Who can say?
Incidentally…
I was hoping Buncho
would have an interview with our Aso.
As part of marketing
for his international debut?
Can I count on you?
Anytime.
I'll be sure to return
the favor however I can.
Let us both…
make the best of this partnership.
Agreed.
Thank you for the generous meal.
Excuse me.
Hello.
Any progress on that matter?
I talked to her last night.
I'll get right to the point.
Our agency's understanding
is that Hideto Aso did not commit
any kind of sexual assault.
We're told that
it was entirely consensual.
If you were to try
and publicize this allegation,
we might be forced to pursue
a lawsuit against you for defamation.
But if you're willing to settle
this matter outside of court,
we will compensate you for any
emotional distress you may have suffered
as a result of this misunderstanding.
Can you agree to a settlement?
I need some time to think.
I expect she'll agree.
Expect?
She said she needed time to think.
She'll respond at a later date.
We'll start marketing efforts
for Aso's international debut soon.
You do understand
that scandals of this nature
are even more taboo overseas
than in Japan, yes?
Of course, ma'am.
This is a critical period.
We can't afford any mistakes.
I know.
Excuse me.
Can you send room service to Room 3908?
Yes, sir.
Where are you?
The Royal Prince Hotel.
Is it true?
Mr. Aso committed sexual assault,
and Fujiwara's scandal was leaked
to cover that up?
We don't have any conclusive proof.
But everything would make sense
if that was true.
It's not unheard of for big agencies
to make deals with publishers
to suppress a scandal by providing them
with another scandal in exchange.
The person behind the cover-up
was most likely their CEO, Yoko Kodama.
The boss herself?
Aso is the face of their agency.
She'd stop at nothing
to keep him out of trouble.
Unbelievable.
That's just horrible.
Mori.
If what you're saying is true,
Aso's agency covered up his sexual assault
by selling out Mr. Fujiwara
and destroying his career.
Everything they've done is awful.
They can't just get away with it!
They won't.
Of course not.
Then…
Ma'am.
Are you going to expose
Aso's sexual assault allegations?
That's too reckless!
We're already being persecuted
by Kodama Productions!
If we defy them any further,
they will take more severe measures,
and we won't be able to survive!
Hirata from Weekly Buncho
said she'd cooperate.
You mean the reporter
who wrote the article on Fujiwara?
We can't trust her!
If we don't do anything about it,
our agency is done for.
And beyond that,
this doesn't concern only us.
This case is just the tip of the iceberg.
Complaints raised by those
who've been unjustly hurt
are being erased
by favoritism and manipulation.
We can't just sit back and let it happen!
I refuse to avert my eyes.
Morning.
-Good morning.
-Morning.
Good morning.
Ninomiya, can I talk to you?
Yeah.
So? What is it?
What is this?
INVOICE AMOUNT: 3,000,000 YEN
Where did you…
I found it in your room.
Three million yen
from the editing department.
Says it's payment for a draft,
but the amount is too high.
Were you bribed by the editor-in-chief?
-I don't know what you mean.
-Don't play dumb!
You tried to write an article
on Aso's sexual assault.
But the editor-in-chief is connected
to Yoko Kodama and stopped you.
Three million yen for your silence.
And to the editor-in-chief,
Yoko Kodama offered a scandal on Fujiwara
she had bought off someone in the past,
which I wrote an article on.
You knew it all, but you kept quiet.
Am I wrong?
You won't deny it?
I'll follow up
on Hideto Aso's sexual assault allegation.
Give me the informant's contact info.
I can't.
Did you agree not to tell anyone,
so you could get the money?
How hard do you think it was
for the victim to speak up
about what happened?
"Surely Buncho would let the world know."
Have you considered
how she felt, being betrayed like that?
You could've taken it to another publisher
if ours wouldn't work.
So why?
I didn't want to back off either.
-Then why--
-I don't have a company protecting me.
If Kodama Productions wanted,
a freelancer like me
would have nowhere to go!
You should stop too.
You'll get kicked out of the company.
Is that all?
Fine.
I think it's almost certain
that Kodama Productions forced
Buncho to suppress the article.
Are you sure?
I'll try to find a way to contact
the informant who came to Buncho,
but there's a risk, our editor-in-chief
could fill Yoko Kodama in on my moves,
so I can't be too conspicuous.
I understand.
We'll try to take action on our end too,
but I'm curious how Kodama Pro will act.
Agreed. I'm certain that they will try
to track down the informant
and try to settle or buy her silence.
We have to make sure we don't fall behind.
Mr. Aso, Mr. Ichinose, it's time.
This way.
Good to go.
-Ready here.
-Thank you.
SAKI IOKA
ONE MISSED CALL
-Good to go.
-Thank you.
Ioka.
-Sorry I'm late.
-No, I'm sorry for calling so suddenly.
This way.
So what did you want to talk about?
I heard through the grapevine
that a scandal on Mr. Aso
might be coming out.
What kind?
I don't know that much.
But I hear it was leaked recently
by someone involved in it,
and Buncho is trying
to verify it right now.
That got me a little concerned.
You okay?
Yeah. It's probably just some rumor.
I would've heard before you
if it was something like that.
-That's true.
-Yeah.
Here you go.
Thanks.
And you, ma'am?
I'm good, thanks.
The number you have dialed can't respond--
HIDETO ASO
Good afternoon.
Man, I'm tired.
-Mizuguchi.
-Yes?
What was she like? That woman
who met Mr. Ninomiya a while back?
-What?
-Did you see her? Know her name?
I only saw her for an instant.
Right.
Wait, let me guess.
Are you into Mr. Ninomiya?
What?
Now I get it. So it's like that.
-No, it's not.
-Yamamoto!
Sir?
By the way, did you hear?
The editor-in-chief
is going to be promoted
to managing director.
-What?
-Becoming a managing director at that age?
How do you think he managed that?
Hirata!
Coming.
This is still off-the-record,
but Kodama Productions' Hideto Aso
will be starring
in a joint US-Japan drama next year.
I see.
We're going to run an interview with Aso
at the same time as its announcement.
You go do it.
What? Me?
They asked for you.
Time is 1:00 p.m. tomorrow. Got it?
Yes.
Pardon me.
I told you last time not to visit me here.
Did you tell anyone
about what we discussed last time?
-I did not.
- Are you sure?
Of course. Why would I?
I await a good response
to the settlement offer.
We'd prefer to avoid
taking any forceful measures.
-Can I get the bill?
-Yes, sir.
Sorry to startle you.
I can't get into details here,
but I have something important
to discuss with you.
PROOF OF RECOLLECTION
KAGAWA
IT WENT WELL
Ms. Hirata.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
It's nice to see you again.
Why me?
Because you're a talented reporter.
That's why I'd love for you
to write an article for us.
I didn't realize
you had such a high opinion of my skills.
Take a seat. And please wait.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Saki Ioka, this agency's CEO.
This is Mr. Tozaki, our lawyer.
Nice to meet you.
A lawyer?
Ms. Riko,
I understand that you were once a talent
under the stage name Risa Hirayama,
affiliated with the agency MK Promotion.
That's correct.
If it's not too personal,
may I ask why you left?
That's…
Were you forced to leave
against your will?
We called you here today to ask you
about an incident you were a victim of.
Do you mean…
The incident with Hideto Aso.
When will you start filming in America?
What?
The filming itself starts in six months,
but there's other prep to be done,
so I'd like to go as soon as possible.
I understand that in this drama,
you'll be playing an anti-hero
who's both charming yet has a cruel side.
It should be new ground for you,
having mostly played
upright characters so far.
Indeed.
It seems the show will also have scenes
with extreme sexual content and violence.
Such scenes are included,
but I'm sure it will be
a challenging venture for me.
Do you see any part of yourself
in the character you'll be portraying?
For example, is there a different side
of you that you can't show to others?
Doesn't everyone have some hidden secret?
You took your story to a magazine
but it went nowhere, as I understand.
We suspect that Buncho's higher-ups
refrained from publishing it
on orders of Kodama Productions.
Shameful conduct for a press company.
It took great courage
for you to disclose it.
It must be frustrating.
Will you try one more time
to get an article published?
It's unacceptable for a victim
to be forced to stay quiet.
We'll help you in whatever way we can.
If you're willing--
I'm already done with it.
I'm going to settle.
Kodama Productions
reached out to me a while back.
And I figured it's been long enough.
So you're giving up?
Don't make it sound so simple.
I've already tried everything I could!
I talked to my manager,
my agency, and even Buncho.
Several times.
But nothing ever came of it.
I'm sure the police
won't take me seriously either.
I might as well take
the money and put this all behind me.
Is that wrong?
And people from Kodama Pro
have been coming to my place of work.
It's a huge bother.
So you'll agree to a settlement?
If you settle, you'll have to sign
a non-disclosure agreement,
which will forbid you
from ever going public with it.
Are you really okay with settling
despite those conditions?
Of course not.
Can you people even imagine it?
I have to see his face on TV
or the Internet, whether I want to or not!
After he…
did that to me…
he gets to smile and bask
in the limelight like it never happened!
How could I ever be okay with that?
But I…
The perpetrator gets protected
while the victim gets silenced.
That's not how it should be.
Aso doesn't deserve to get away
with putting you through all this.
Will you please…
try one more time to go public with this?
I know a reporter who can help.
Thank you for today.
Likewise. It was a pleasure.
Are you free?
Sorry?
We could get a drink at a bar nearby.
I appreciate the offer,
but I still have work to do.
Maybe some other time.
Ms. Hirata.
I hope you'll continue
to have a good relationship
with Aso and our agency.
So do I.
Ma'am, she's here.
Sorry to call you so suddenly.
-The informant is in here.
-Okay.
Do you plan to publish it
in Weekly Buncho?
No, it wouldn't get past
the editor-in-chief at Buncho,
so I'm acting on my own for now.
I'll think about the next steps
after listening to the victim's account.
Understood.
This way.
Sorry for the wait.
Let me introduce you.
This is Ms. Hirata, a reporter.
Why?
It's her?
Yes.
Riko.
What-- Ms. Riko?
I have nothing to say to her.
Wait. Excuse me. Ms. Riko!
Do you know her?
She's my younger sister.
Ms. Riko! Ms. Riko.
What happened? Please talk to me.
-I have nothing to say.
-Please!
Leave me alone.
Thank you.
Riko was scouted by a talent agency
when she was in high school.
She went against our parents' wishes,
and moved to Tokyo
after dropping out of school.
But this industry
is a hard place to survive in.
We never heard her name
in any big announcements.
As our parents grew more worried,
she contacted us less and less.
She didn't even show up
to our father's funeral.
I can't forgive her selfishness
nor the entertainment industry
that lured her in with sweet promises,
then discarded her.
I'm sorry.
I couldn't stop her.
I should go too.
-Wait, but--
-It's okay, Kagawa
But…
Even if they were estranged,
she only just found out
that her own sister was part of all this.
RISA HIRAYAMA
AFTER THE MASTER OF THE MANSION DIED
Hirata.
Finish up Aso's interview
and send it to me.
Yes, sir.
The CEO of Kodama is nagging me,
saying she wants to see the draft.
Thanks.
-Goodbye.
-See you tomorrow.
No word from Ms. Riko?
None.
Here she finally worked up the courage
to talk about it,
but we damaged her trust in us.
It wasn't your fault.
Who could've guessed
that the reporter was her sister?
How about convincing her
to talk to a different reporter?
But I don't know if we should
push her anymore right now.
How will we counter
Kodama Productions then?
Unless we weaken their influence
by exposing Aso's sexual assault,
they'll keep pressuring us.
Call me if there are any updates. Goodbye.
I found something.
What?
Take a look at this.
DOCUMENTARY KODAMA PRODUCTIONS
What's this?
A Kodama Productions audition.
From when Yuri Hara joined.
Yuri Hara?
A talent I was in charge of
back at Kodama Pro.
Wait, but isn't she the one--
I thought I'd seen Ms. Riko before,
so I did some research.
Back there.
Good day.
Mom? What is it?
Kanade?
I wanted to talk to you
about Dad's memorial service.
When will you come home next?
Sorry, I can't say yet.
I'll let you know when I'm sure.
Oh, and also,
have you heard from Riko?
I tried calling her,
but it never goes through.
Just forget her already.
But I'm still worried about her.
I wonder where she is
and what she's doing.
Sorry, Mom.
I'm still at work. Call you later.
Hello?
Doesn't Hirata…
seem strange to you lately?
What?
Doesn't she?
Why would you ask me?
Aren't you two dating?
-What?
-Don't bother playing dumb.
I used to be a reporter too. I can tell.
Did you tell her
about that thing with Aso?
No, of course not.
This is the Aso interview article
that she wrote up.
She didn't go for anything too deep.
Looks to me like she's cautious.
Be honest.
How much has she found out?
I don't know.
I really don't.
-Sorry for calling you so late.
-It's fine.
About what happened this afternoon…
Can I go first?
I'm considering backing out
of the Hideto Aso situation.
I know I'm the one
who brought it up to you, so I apologize.
Is it because your sister is involved?
As a reporter,
I judged that it would be difficult
to keep my personal feelings out of it.
And besides,
I doubt that she would open up to me.
We never exactly got along.
Neither of us wants to see each other.
Do you really…
feel that way?
I have something I want you to see.
What's this?
A video of an old audition
for Kodama Productions.
Keep going!
The one in the back.
That's Ms. Riko.
And two, and three, and four…
I asked the other participants too.
While she didn't pass the audition,
she worked harder than anyone.
Two, three, four.
Five, six, seven, eight.
One, two, three, four.
This industry is special.
Once you enter it, it's not easy
to return to a regular life.
Some people get a lucky break,
while others find no success
despite putting in great effort.
Because you yourself are the product.
If things don't go well, you feel like
your own worth is being rejected.
You wish for validation, grow desperate,
and find yourself trapped.
That's how this industry enchants people.
I don't think Ms. Riko
neglected her family.
I think she kept
struggling the entire time.
So that one day, her family would accept
the path she chose.
What would you understand?
What about you?
Can you really say
you understand Ms. Riko?
It's true that this industry
has a foul side to it,
but most talents
put in everything they've got,
and the management tries to support them.
And yet, some never get accepted.
I'd say I understand
how lonely that can make them feel.
What is it that drives you?
Right.
I left my home against my parents' wish.
I know they must be worried,
so I want to put them at ease
by showing some results.
Thank you.
Thank you too.
-That'll be all.
-Thank you.
YOU HAVE AN UNREAD MESSAGE
RIKO, RIGHT?
THIS IS KANADE. CAN WE TALK?
Hey there.
-You alone?
-Let's drink together.
-Our treat.
-Just one, okay?
Hey. Wait up!
RIKO, RIGHT?
THIS IS KANADE. CAN WE TALK?
Welcome.
-Two coffees.
-Coming right up.
Here it is.
The proposal
for the online drama that Mori got us.
It's not a major production,
but shall we take it?
Let's give it a try.
I hope it works out.
We have to keep ourselves afloat,
even if it's through small jobs.
Ma'am?
In this industry, only few people succeed
even after passing strict auditions.
Most of them
just exhaust themselves and fade away.
That's…
You know what Yuri's parents
said to me at her funeral?
"You people are monsters."
Ms. Yuri's death wasn't your fault.
I should've been with her more.
I don't want to avoid responsibility.
I wonder what our job even is.
-Vodka tonic.
-Hey!
Listen.
Don't ignore me.
You're annoying. Go away.
What?
-Watch it, you--
-Wait.
-She's Risa Hirayama.
-Who?
She was a pin-up model,
for a little while.
Yikes. And now she's drinking booze alone
at a place like this?
Oh, what a poor thing.
Hey, I have an idea.
How about you do porn?
You'll be way more successful.
-Good idea.
-Right?
Hey, relax.
Hey! What's your problem?
-Calm down!
-Stop it!
-What the heck?
-Let go!
Let me go!
-Calm down!
-Let go!
RIKO, RIGHT?
THIS IS KANADE. CAN WE TALK?
Hello?
I'm sorry for the trouble.
Why did you come?
You think I deserve it, don't you?
I don't.
You think I'm pathetic and miserable.
Look, I don't.
You do. You always have.
You've always looked down on me,
like you knew better.
You'd never understand how I feel.
Of course not!
I never did.
I didn't even try.
I had no idea how you felt
as you continued struggling.
Even if you have the skill and work hard,
things don't always work out.
No matter how desperate you get,
reality is all too often cruel.
But you stayed true to yourself
and did the best you could
without accepting defeat.
Isn't that right?
That's why…
I'm sorry.
For not being able to notice anything.
It must have been so hard, all this time.
You should come home.
Mom is worried about you.
I still have unfinished business.
Unfinished business?
I want to expose Aso.
In the end, I can't forgive him.
I want you…
to write the article.
Please.
You monster!
HARA FAMILY
Hello?
They are waiting for you.
Thanks.
Ms. Riko.
I'm sorry about last time.
It's okay.
The two of us talked things out.
And we decided…
I will tell you everything
that happened to me.
Only one person knows
I'm investigating this story.
PREVIEW
I… I'll live my life my own way!
THE SECRET PAST IS REVEALED
She likely won't agree to settle.
You think Kodama Productions
is behind this?
CHANGING FACTS AS FAKE JUSTICE
Do you really find that acceptable?
I will never
be able to regain control of my life.
You mean Ioka is also involved in this?
Are you Riko Hirata?
I won't let Kodama Pro do as they please.
I can hear you out if you want.
A SLIVER OF HOPE TURNS FATE AROUND
I'll try one more time
to make this into an article.
Ms. Yoko won't try to sabotage me again,
will she?
You're still on that?
What about my standing?
Ma'am!
But how…?
THE TRUTH CHANGES INSTANTLY
Let's put a stop to this absurd injustice.
KANADE'S SISTER, RIKO HIRATA,
IS THE VICTIM OF THIS INCIDENT
DARKNESS LOOMS OVER HER
AS A CRUEL TRAP PREYS ON HER EMOTIONS
Subtitle translation by: Saim Ul Hassan